

## **CONTACT**

#### +358 403 714 613

kozliakova.kat@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/Radistka https://www.behance.net/Katya\_rad3715 https://www.github.com/Rudakop

https://www.plandent.fi
https://www.sampo.com
https://2022.digitalasnallkalendern.art/login
https://www.tuska.fi

#### **IT SKILLS**

JavaScript Angular, Vue, React React Native Redux, React, JS, Jest TypeScript, Bootstrap HTML,CSS SQL,NoSQL AWS, Azure DevOps Terraform Git, Docker, CI/CD Agile, Scrum VSC, VS, Webstorm Photoshop Figma, Illustrator Contentful, Optimizely WordPress MS Office Power Point, Excel C#, Python Node JS, Next JS

#### **LANGUAGES**

English: Full working proficiency Finnish: Full working proficiency

Ukrainian: Basic

#### **REFERENCES**

Siret Matsina +358404829898 Customer Lead Create CX siret.matsina@tietoevry.com

### **EDUCATION**

09/2002 - 05/2007 Master's Degree State University of Engineering and Economics

# KATJA KOZLIAKOVA

### **ABOUT ME**

Goal-oriented person with more than 3 years of experience in project work in web design and 3 years in software development. In 2018, I moved to Finland, after which I studied the Finnish language full-time for 1.5 years, in order to achieve a good language level and citizenship.

My core competencies are a strong desire to learn new things and develop own skills, a can-do attitude and responsibility.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# 11/2023 – 05/2024 Low-code system development expert, Taitopalo Oy

• planning, implementing and publicizing the online service PowerPlatform, Power Apps, SQL, Dynamics 365, Power BI, HTML/CSS, Python, Wordpress, JS, MS Office.

#### 05/2023 - 11/2023 own sw project

• creating own web portfolio: React, emailJS, greensock animations and complex styling.

### 11/2021 – 05/2023 Full-Stack Developer, Tietoevry Oy

- maintenance and full-stack development for international web shop net with headless cms Optimizely v11, using C#, and Vue;
- bug fixing, testing, implementation of different kinds of web shop's functionality, for example search and quick-search functionality;
- full-stack development from scratch of new website financial service provider using React, Typescript, Bootstrap, Optimizely v12;
- front end development with high-quality responsive implementation of created web design for Open page 2021/22 for famous financial service provider, considering big data reporting;
- participating in public sector's project of Native Android/iOS development React Native, Contentful;
- participating in competitive project using headless cms Optimizely v11, HTML and CSS, Figma

#### 03/2021 – 08/2021 SW Developer, Nomentia Oy

- programming and creating from text pages to fixing complex bugs using React, HTML, CSS, SQL, Java Script and JS-frameworks
- making user interfaces both user-friendly and functional discussing it with team and designer
- using VSC, VS, docker, kubernetes, Jenkins, Azure DevOps

# 10/2020 – 03/2021 Frontend Web Developer, UI/UX Designer, PHZ Full-stack Oy

• programming with Angular in real customer's project and converting UI/UX designs to responsive HTML/CSS, React, using Material UI; for professional developing I'm studding more programming languages C#